tizianafausti.com 2018-12-26

# Tiziana Fausti

## PRIVACY

All personal data supplied by the client will be treated in full respect of privacy regulations. In particular, Exor Inc. S.r.l. - With registered office in Portici Sentierone 43 , 24121 Bergamo - owner of the site Tizianafausti.com claims to use the personal information provided voluntarily by the customer, according to legislative decree no. No 196 of 30 June 2003 ( "Code regarding the protection of personal data") which provides for the protection of persons and other subjects regarding the processing of personal data. Under the legislation, such treatment will be based on principles of correctness, lawfulness and transparency and the protection of privacy and rights of the Customer. And to that end, Tiziana Fausti will not distribute or sell online personal information to third parties, without prejudice to any legal requirements and technical needs related to the provision and management of e-commerce service.  The data controller is the legal representative of Exor Inc. S.r.l., in the person of Fausti Tiziana. The treatment will be achieved with the aid of computerized by the owner and operators of this charge and is designed provide the services requested, the activity of sale of goods, the compilation of statistics on the use of such services and - if this has been specifically authorized - sending promotional information, either in digital or paper (if the paper is provided).  Providing data from the Customer is required to be able to follow the business, and refusing to provide such data involves the breach of the contract of sale.  At any moment it will be possible for the client ask for the verification, cancellation, modification of their data, or receive the list of processors, writing an email to SHOPONLINE@TIZIANAFAUSTI.COM or written communication addressed to Exor Inc.Srl - Portici Sentierone 43 to 24,121 Bergamo.  In addition to comply with all obligations under the Legislative Decree no. 196/2003, Tiziana Fausti also ensures the utmost attention to data protection from fraudulent access and the immediate cancellation from their lists in response to a request to do so by the Customer in any time to exercise their rights against the holder treatment under Article 7 of Legislative Decree 196/2003, reproduced here in full:   
Legislative Decree No. 196/2003, Article 7 - Right of access to personal data and other rights.  
1\. You have the right to obtain confirmation of whether or not personal data concerning him, even if not yet recorded, and their communication in intelligible form.   
2\. You have the right to obtain information:   
a) about the origin of personal data;  
b) about the purposes and methods of treatment;  
c) about logic applied in case of treatment with the help of electronic means;  
d) about the identity of the owner, manager and the representative appointed under article 5, paragraph 2;  
e)about subjects or categories of persons to whom personal data may be communicated or who can learn about them as appointed representative in the State, managers or agents.  
3\. The individual has the right to:   
a) updating, rectification or, when interested, integration of data;   
b) cancellation, transformation into anonymous form or blocking of data processed unlawfully, including data which need not be kept for the purposes for which data were collected or subsequently processed;   
c) certification that the operations in letters a) and b) have been notified, including their contents, to those to whom the data were communicated or disseminated, except where this requirement proves impossible or involves means manifestly disproportionate to the protected right.   
4\. You have the right to object, in whole or in part:  
a) for legitimate reasons the processing of personal data concerning him, even to the scope of the collection;  
b) the processing of personal data that concerns him for the purpose of sending advertising materials or direct selling or for carrying out market research or commercial communication

**POLICY FOR PROCESSING OF PERSONAL DATA**

Pursuant to and by the effect of Article 13 of the New European Regulation 2016/679 concerning the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data (GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION – GDPR).

As required by the General Data Protection Regulation of the European Union (GDPR 2016/679, Article 13), before proceeding with processing, the interested party (User of the website www.tizianafausti.com) is informed that personal data collected through the website are subject to processing by the Company through IT and/or telematic tools, for the purposes indicated in this policy.

To this end, the User is presented with the Privacy Policy prepared by EXOR IN SRL. (hereafter as “TIZIANA FAUSTI” or “the Company” or “the Data Controller”), creator and promoter of the activities available on the website www.tizianafausti.com.

**Data Controller**

The Data Controller for personal data is EXOR INC SRL. – registered office in Via Portici Sentierone, 43 – 24121, Bergamo, Italy – email shoponline@tizianafausti.com.

For further information regarding the rights of the interested party, please consider the paragraph entitled “Rights of Interested Party” of this policy.

**Information Processing**

The personal data subject to processing is collected directly by EXOR INC SRL or by third parties expressly authorized by the Data Controller, or communicated by the Company to such third parties for the pursuit of the purposes described below.

**Legal Basis and Purpose of Processing**

The personal data provided by the User when browsing the website www.tizianafausti.com are processed by the Data Controller in accordance with the current regulations for the protection of personal data.

The legal basis of the processing is identified in the provision of its services by the Company, in the management and facilitation of the website, as well as in the establishment, execution and possible termination of online sales contract concluded between the parties, and in the obligations of the same contract connected either directly and/or indirectly deriving from it.

The processing of your personal data by EXOR INC SRL is aimed at pursuing the following purposes:

**1)** **SUBSCRIPTION TO THE TIZIANA FAUSTI NEWSLETTER:** In the case that you decide to subscribe to the “TIZIANA FAUSTI Newsletter”, only after your express and specific consent, your personal data will be processed by the Data Controller for sending of commercial or promotional communications, relative updates, for example, to the latest trends, new arrivals, exclusive offers, special events and promotions. To unsubscribe from the newsletter simply click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the emails received or by writing to shoponline@tizianafausti.com.

**2)** **REGISTRATION ON TIZIANAFAUSTI.COM:** In the case that you decide to register on the website www.tizianafausti.com, only after your express and specific consent, personal data will be processed by the Data Controller for the purpose of registration on www.tizianafausti.com. In particular, in providing your name, last name, email address and the setting of an access password, these will be processed for the creation of your personal account, to speed up the purchase process, to allow you to view the status of orders and receive updates on purchases made, as well as change personal settings and update your account, view the history of returns and requests for the exchange of goods, save favorite items in your Wishlist and allow you to join at a later time, if the desired, to the loyalty program, TIZIANA FAUSTI VIP PROGRAM.

**3) ONLINE SHOPPING ACTIVITIES:** The personal data you provide will be used for the establishment, management, execution and/or conclusion of the online sales contract. The data you provide will be processed by the Data Controller for the purpose of managing the purchase order with reference to, for example, payment, shipment, management of returns, customer support, administrative and accounting purposes related to the management of the order and the fulfillment of obligations under the current legislation. In case of payment by credit card, the fundamental information for the execution of the transaction (credit/debit card number, expiration date, security code) will be processed by Banca Sella, Paypal or, possibly, by companies in charge of the anti-fraud control using an encrypted protocol and without any third parties being able to access it in any way. This information will never be displayed or stored by the seller EXOR INC SRL.

**4) PROFILING OF THE PHYSICAL PERSON:** Only after your express and explicit consent, the personal data you provided may be processed by the Data Controller for profiling activities, or analysis of your preferences aimed at creating personalized content and offers.

**Nature of Processing**

In relation to the purposes referenced in point 1) of the previous section, providing your personal data and consent to its processing is optional. Failure to provide consent will make it impossible for EXOR INC SRL to allow you to subscribe to the “TIZIANA FAUSTI Newsletter”, to send commercial or promotional communications, updates on, for example, latest trends, new arrivals, exclusive offers, special events and promotions.

If you decide to proceed with the newsletter subscription through the section of the website solely dedicated to this activity, the provision of your personal data and consent to their treatment is mandatory.

Failure to provide the consent will make it impossible for EXOR INC SRL to allow you to subscribe to the “TIZIANA FAUSTI Newsletter”, to send commercial or promotional communications, updates on, for example, latest trends, new arrivals, exclusive offers, special events and promotions.

In relation to the purposes referenced in point 2) of the previous section, providing your personal data and consent to its processing is mandatory.

Failure to provide consent will make it impossible for EXOR INC SRL to allow you to register with www.tizianafausti.com, create a personal account, speed up the purchase process, view the status of orders and receive updates on purchases, the possibility to update personal settings and account preferences, view the history of returns and exchange requests, save favorite items in the Wishlist or to enroll in later, if you so wish, the loyalty program TIZIANA FAUSTI VIP PROGRAM.

In relation to the purposes referenced in point 3) of the previous section, providing your personal data and consent to its processing is optional.

Failure to provide your consent will make it impossible for EXOR INC SRL to allow you to join the loyalty program TIZIANA FAUSTI PRIVILEGE.

In relation to the purposes referenced in point 4) of the previous section, providing your personal data and consent to its processing is mandatory.

Failure to provide the consent will make it impossible for EXOR INC SRL to proceed with the establishment, management, execution and/or conclusion of the online sales contract, therefore making it impossible to perform, for example, activities related to payment, shipment, management of returns, customer support, administrative and accounting purposes related to the management of the order and the fulfillment of obligations under current legislation.

In relation to the purposes referenced in point 5) of the previous section, providing your personal data and consent to its processing is optional.

Failure to provide consent will make it impossible for EXOR INC SRL to perform profiling activities, or to perform analysis of your preferences aimed at creating personalized content and offers.

**Personal Data Processing**

The Data Controller processes the personal data provided by the User when browsing the website www.tizianafausti.com, in the event of any registration/subscription to the services/programs made available by EXOR INC SRL and/or the possible purchase of goods made available by EXOR INC SRL. Examples of personal data are name, last name and email address, in addition to the data necessary for the conclusion of the online sales contract, such as: the functional data for the execution of payment, shipment and exchange of purchased goods.

**Methods of Processing and Storing Data**

The processing of personal data is performed by the Data Controller in compliance with the provisions of the current legislation on Privacy. The Data Controller processes personal data using IT and/or telematic tools and with organizational and logical procedures strictly related to the purposes indicated in this policy, as well as adopting the appropriate security measures to prevent access, disclosure, unauthorized modification or destruction of personal data, its loss and its illicit and incorrect use. However, the Company cannot guarantee its Users that the measures taken for website security and the transmission of data and information on the website are capable of limiting or excluding any risk of unauthorized access or loss of data by devices pertaining to the User. For this reason, it is suggested that the Users of the website make sure that their computer is equipped with adequate software to protect the transmission of data (such as updated antivirus) and that its Internet provider has adopted appropriate measures for the security of the transmission of data on the network. The Company also undertakes to process the data according to the principles of correctness, lawfulness and transparency, to collect the data to the extent necessary and exact for processing and to allow its use only by personnel for authorized purposes. The management and storage of personal data acquired will take place in archives or on servers located within the European Union owned by the Data Controller and/or by third-party companies appointed as External Data Processor for processing and, in any case, currently located in Italy.

In relation to the different purposes for which data is collected, personal data will be kept for the time strictly necessary to achieve that purpose and, in any case, in accordance with the current relevant regulations.

In any case, the Company will take care to avoid the use of data indefinitely by proceeding, on a regular basis, to verify appropriately the effective permanence of the interest of the User to which they refer.

**Data Processors and Recipients**

The data collected will not be disseminated in any way, but will be treated within the limits and for the purposes described by the employees of the Company on the basis of appropriate operating instructions (for example, administrative, commercial, marketing, legal personnel, system administrators, etc.). Some data processing may also be performed by third parties, appointed as External Data Processors for processing, of which the Data Controller relies on or could be used in the management of the contractual relationship, the provision of services offered and organizational needs of its activities. In particular, the data could be communicated to:

a) Persons, public and private, that can access the data by virtue of the provision of law, regulation or community legislation, within the limits set by these rules;

b) Persons who need access to data for purposes related to the contractual relationship existing between the parties, within the limits strictly necessary for the performance of auxiliary tasks (such as, for example, banks and lenders, technical service providers, hosting providers, IT companies, communication agencies, mail carriers and shipping companies);

c) Consultants, within the limits necessary for carrying out their professional duties.

The updated list of External Data Processors and other persons authorized to process the data is kept at the Data Controller’s registered office and is available to the interested party, following a request sent via email to shoponline@tizianafausti.com.

**Transfer of Data Abroad**

The management and storage of personal data will be carried out on servers of the Owner and/or third-party companies duly appointed as External Data Processors located within the European Union.

Your personal data may be transferred abroad, in accordance with the provisions of current legislation, even in countries outside the European Union.

The transfer to countries outside the EU, in addition to cases in which this is guaranteed by an Adequacy Decisions by the Commission, is carried out in such a way as to provide appropriate and opportune guarantees pursuant to Articles 46, 47 or 49 of the Regulation.

Rights of Interested Party – As the interested party, you may exercise, at any time, the rights provided to you in Articles 15, 16, 17, 18, 20 and 21 of the GDPR which, in particular, confer the rights to:

a) Obtain from the Data Controller, pursuant to Article 15, confirmation of the existence or not of personal data being processed and, in this case, obtain access to the data and information such as: (i) the purposes of the processing; (ii) the categories of personal data; (iii) the recipients or categories of recipients to whom the personal data have been or will be disclosed, in particular recipients located in Third Countries or International Organizations; (iv) when possible, the retention period of the personal data provided or, if not possible, the criteria used to determine this period;

b) Obtain from the Data Controller, pursuant to Article 16, the correction of inaccurate personal data without undue delay; taking into account the purposes of the processing, the data subject has the right to have incomplete personal data completed, by providing an additional declaration;

c) Obtain from the Data Controller, pursuant to Article 17, the deletion of their personal data without undue delay. The Owner has the obligation to cancel, without undue delay, personal data if there is one of the reasons indicated in paragraph 1 of Article 17;

d) Obtain from the Data Controller, pursuant to Article 18, restriction of processing when one of the hypotheses governed by paragraph 1 of Article 18 occurs;

e) Obtain from the Data Controller, pursuant to Article 20, the portability of data or to receive in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format, their personal data provided to a Data Controller. The Data Subject also has the right to transmit such data to another Data Controller without impediments by the first Data Controller to whom it has provided them, if the conditions indicated in Article 20 paragraph 1 are met. Finally, the Data Subject has the right to obtain the direct transmission of personal data from one Data Controller to another, if technically feasible;

f) Object to, in whole or in part, pursuant to Article 21, the processing of their personal data.

To exercise these rights, the User can send their requests to shoponline@tizianafausti.com.

It should also be noted that the Data Subject has the right to revoke the consent at any time without prejudice to the lawfulness of the processing based on the consent given prior to the revocation, without prejudice to the consequences indicated above regarding a refusal to provide such personal data. The Data Subject also has the right to lodge a complaint with a Control Authority.

You can make requests regarding these rights by contacting the Data Controller at the email address shoponline@tizianafausti.com.

EXOR INC SRL will respond to requests made by the interested party within one month, except in cases of particular complexity, for which it may take up to a maximum of three months. In any case, the Data Controller will provide the interested party with the reason for the delayed response within one month of the request. The outcome of the request will be provided in writing or in electronic format. In case of request for rectification, cancellation and limitation of processing, the Data Controller will communicate the results of the requests received by the Data Subject to each of the recipients of their data, unless this proves impossible or involves a disproportionate effort.

The Company specifies that a contribution may be requested from the Interested Party if the applications manifest to be unfounded, excessive or repetitive; in this regard, the Data Controller will provide a register to track the requests for intervention.

**Changes to this Policy**

The data controller reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time by giving notice to users on the website www.tizianafausti.com. Therefore, please consult this page often, referring to the date of last modification indicated at the bottom of the policy. In case of non-acceptance of the changes made to this Privacy Policy, the Data Subject may request the Data Controller to delete their personal data. Unless otherwise specified, the previous Privacy Policy will continue to apply to personal data collected until then.

Privacy Policy updated on 24 May 2018

Exor Inc. S.R.L. - C.F. e P.IVA 04185700160 - Portici Sentierone 43, 24121 Bergamo (IT)
